<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Warframe News on Warframe Blog</title>
    <link>https://warframeblog.com/warframe-news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Warframe News on Warframe Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 00:45:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://warframeblog.com/warframe-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Prime Vault Opening July 24 - Rhino Prime &amp; Nyx Prime.</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/prime-vault-unsealed-rhino-nyx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 13:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/prime-vault-unsealed-rhino-nyx/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys and welcome to another Warframe news article. Today I want to talk a little bit about Prime Vault because it will reopen once again on the 24th of July. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limbo Prime Access Is Here. New Relics Drop Table</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/limbo-prime-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 23:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/limbo-prime-access/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys and welcome to another Warframe article. So, Limbo Prime, &lt;a href=&#34;https://warframeblog.com/pyrana-prime-build/&#34;&gt;Pyrana Prime&lt;/a&gt;, and Destreza Prime are finally here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update 23 Overview: The Sacrifice</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/update-23-the-sacrifice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 18:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/update-23-the-sacrifice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys and welcome to another Warframe news article. And the Sacrifice update is finally here and it brought a bunch of new stuff. So, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about it in a spoiler-free manner as possible without actually skipping over any of the features. I won&amp;rsquo;t talk about the Sacrifice Quest or what happens in the Sacrifice Quest. I will let you discover that on your own but I will talk about the items that you end up with at the end.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Razorbacks Armada Returns Once More</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/the-razorbacks-armada-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 04:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/the-razorbacks-armada-event/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys and welcome to another Warframe article and The Razorback Armada event has returned or should I say the Razorback is back?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zephyr Prime Access Is Here. New Relics Drop Table</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/zephyr-prime-access-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 13:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/zephyr-prime-access-is-here/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys and welcome to another Warframe article. And Zephyr Prime, Tiberon Prime, and Kronen Prime are finally here. And they are absolutely glorious. My favorite one is probably the&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zephyr Prime Access Begins March 20</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/zephyr-prime-access-begins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 01:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/zephyr-prime-access-begins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys and welcome to another Warframe article and the newest Prime warframe has been revealed and it is the one and only Zephyr Prime. Oh yes, the mighty bird the poor bird that was supposed to be Primed a long ago but we got Mirage Prime instead.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arcane Rework - Update 22.14.0</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/arcane-rework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 23:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/arcane-rework/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys! Welcome to another Warframe article. And update 22.14.0 is here and while it doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem like a massive patch the changes that it did bring are pretty big. And the biggest change that was introduced with this update by far is the removal of Raids first of all and second of all the arcane rework.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eidolons Now Drop Arcane Enhancements</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/eidolons-drop-arcane-enhancements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 19:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/eidolons-drop-arcane-enhancements/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys. Welcome to another Warframe article. And I was browsing the Warframe forum yesterday and out of nowhere, this cheeky little bugger of a hotfix 22.13.2 popped up. Now, I don&amp;rsquo;t really understand why this is labeled as a hotfix because it actually has a pretty major feature. In that, they finally added the arcane enchantments to the drop tables of all three eidolons. And I don&amp;rsquo;t know about you but to me, that doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel like a hotfix that feels like a pretty major change right there.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prime Vault Unsealed - Ember, Frost &amp; Loki. New Relics Drop Table</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/prime-vault-unsealed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 13:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/prime-vault-unsealed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys! Welcome to another Warframe article and the Prime Vault has opened up yet again so you can now farm: &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warframe Update 22.9 Quartakk Buff</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/warframe-update-22-9-quartakk-buff/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 21:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/warframe-update-22-9-quartakk-buff/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys and welcome to another Warframe article. An update 22.9 has arrived two days ago and, oh my, it has a lot of TennoGen. I particularly like the Vauban Graxx Skin by Faven, I might actually buy that one.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Acolytes Are Back Again. Acolyte Mods</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/acolytes-back-acolyte-mods/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 00:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/acolytes-back-acolyte-mods/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi guys and welcome to another Warframe article. And the acolytes have returned yet again.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warframe Focus 2.5</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/warframe-new-focus-2-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 14:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/warframe-new-focus-2-5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys and welcome to another Warframe article. Update 22.6 came out a few hours ago and yet again, we got our Focus Points refunded.. for a good reason. The reason for that is Focus 2.5. But what exactly changed?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>