<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Categories on Warframe Blog</title>
    <link>https://warframeblog.com/categories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Categories on Warframe Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 14:03:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://warframeblog.com/categories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Primes</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/primes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 19:43:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/primes/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Builds</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/builds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/builds/</guid>
      <description>Want to build Warfame or Weapon in order to get maximum efficiency out of it? Or perhaps you got a new Weapon or Warframe and don&amp;rsquo;t know how to build it right? Well, then this is the page you are looking for! It contains lots of Warframe Builds as well as Weapon Builds. And all of these builds are waiting for you to check them out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melee Weapon Builds</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/melee-weapon-builds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/melee-weapon-builds/</guid>
      <description>Every Melee Weapon in Warframe you can build in a thousand alternative ways, and there is plenty of room to tweak it on your end, therefore please don&amp;rsquo;t take it as if the Weapon Builds below are no longer changeable. You can copy any build exactly, and it&amp;rsquo;s going to work fine, of course, but I&amp;rsquo;d think of Melee Weapon Builds below as more of an inspiration for your builds because you can play around with different values: critical chance, attack speed, status chance, critical multiplier, damage, and even type of damage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primary Weapon Builds</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/primary-weapon-builds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/primary-weapon-builds/</guid>
      <description>Every Primary Weapon in Warframe you can build in a thousand alternative ways, and there is plenty of room to tweak it on your end, therefore please don&amp;rsquo;t take it as if the Weapon Builds below are no longer changeable. You can copy any build exactly, and it&amp;rsquo;s going to work fine, of course, but I&amp;rsquo;d think of Primary Weapon Builds below as more of an inspiration for your builds because you can play around with different values: critical chance, status chance, critical multiplier, damage, and even type of damage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secondary Weapon Builds</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/secondary-weapon-builds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/secondary-weapon-builds/</guid>
      <description>Every Secondary Weapon in Warframe you can build in a thousand various ways, and there is plenty of room to tweak it on your end, therefore please don&amp;rsquo;t take it as if the Weapon Builds below were carved in stone. You can copy any build precisely, and it&amp;rsquo;s going to work fine, of course, but I&amp;rsquo;d think of Secondary Weapon Builds below as more of an inspiration for your builds because you can play around with different values: critical chance, status chance, critical multiplier, damage, and even type of damage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warframe Builds</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/warframe-builds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/warframe-builds/</guid>
      <description>Each warframe you can build in a thousand different ways and there’s a lot of room for tweaking on your end, so please don’t take it as if builds below were set in stone. You can of course copy builds exactly and it’s going to work just fine, but I would think about Warframe Builds below as more of an inspiration for your own builds because you can play around with different values: duration, efficiency, range, and even strength.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warframe Farming</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/farming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 00:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/farming/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warframe Guides</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/guides/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 00:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/guides/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warframe News</title>
      <link>https://warframeblog.com/warframe-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 00:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://warframeblog.com/warframe-news/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>